And what I'm going to do also JR is I'm going to apply a papaya and pineapple enzyme peel onto your skin.
I'm just going to warm it up a little bit before I put it on.
I don't want to shock you with a cold product.
Now, with steam, can people at home do their own steam, like I always see women with a pot over their head, leaning down with a towel over the pot.
Oh sure, yeah you can steam your own skin at home.
It's fine.
It opens the pores.
It makes it easier to clean the skin and it also, it also helps to make it, and it really helps with perspiration as well.
So it cleans the skin out and you just want to make sure that you do a good cleanse before you steam.
Is it good for people with oily skin?
Actually, steam is very good for oily skin.
It also helps to cleanse the skin and soften it, and it helps anything that you have that's clogging the pores to come out.
So someone who has acne skin, steam is good for it as well because that's obviously problems with maybe pores that are clogged or just hormones and things like that so it'll help the product to take deeper into the skin.
That's correct.
Yes.
You want to, you want to be careful with acne skin though because you, you want, you want to cleanse it and you want to put the right products on there.
A lot of people think that if you have acne prone skin that you can't use any moisturizer.
Moisturizers are fine for acne prone skin.
What they do is, they really help to balance the ph of the skin and by doing that you're allowing the skin to produce the proper amount of oil.
Sometimes if it's dried out too much it's going to produce more oils naturally and as a result tend to be even oilier than if you hadn't used a moisturizer.
Exactly.